{
    "inputTimeWaitSecs": 90,
    "openingRemarks": "Enter answer as space or comma separated pair of integers.<p>NB: You can also enter 'U' or 'unexpected' if no pair of integers exist to satisfy the demands of the question.",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 14 and whose sum is -9.",
        "answer": "-7 -2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 7 and whose sum is -8.",
        "answer": "-1 -7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 30 and whose sum is 28.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 18 and whose sum is 9.",
        "answer": "6 3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 9 and whose sum is 6.",
        "answer": "3 3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -12 and whose sum is -4.",
        "answer": "2 -6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 12 and whose sum is -7.",
        "answer": "-4 -3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 20 and whose sum is 9.",
        "answer": "5 4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 1 and whose sum is -2.",
        "answer": "-1 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 6 and whose sum is -5.",
        "answer": "-2 -3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -8 and whose sum is -2.",
        "answer": "-4 2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -4 and whose sum is 3.",
        "answer": "4 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 14 and whose sum is 9.",
        "answer": "7 2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -5 and whose sum is 4.",
        "answer": "5 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 35 and whose sum is 12.",
        "answer": "5 7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 2 and whose sum is 2.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -6 and whose sum is -5.",
        "answer": "1 -6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 1 and whose sum is 1.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 6 and whose sum is 7.",
        "answer": "6 1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 24 and whose sum is -10.",
        "answer": "-6 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -6 and whose sum is 1.",
        "answer": "-2 3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 30 and whose sum is -11.",
        "answer": "-5 -6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -35 and whose sum is 2.",
        "answer": "-5 7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -5 and whose sum is 3.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 10 and whose sum is -7.",
        "answer": "-2 -5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -10 and whose sum is -3.",
        "answer": "2 -5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 42 and whose sum is 13.",
        "answer": "7 6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 35 and whose sum is -12.",
        "answer": "-7 -5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -28 and whose sum is 3.",
        "answer": "7 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -24 and whose sum is 2.",
        "answer": "6 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 2 and whose sum is -3.",
        "answer": "-2 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -35 and whose sum is -2.",
        "answer": "5 -7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 8 and whose sum is -6.",
        "answer": "-2 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 4 and whose sum is 5.",
        "answer": "1 4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -5 and whose sum is -4.",
        "answer": "1 -5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 3 and whose sum is -4.",
        "answer": "-3 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 49 and whose sum is 14.",
        "answer": "7 7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 25 and whose sum is -10.",
        "answer": "-5 -5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 4 and whose sum is 4.",
        "answer": "2 2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 8 and whose sum is 6.",
        "answer": "2 4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -18 and whose sum is 3.",
        "answer": "-3 6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 42 and whose sum is -13.",
        "answer": "-6 -7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -2 and whose sum is 1.",
        "answer": "2 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -15 and whose sum is 2.",
        "answer": "5 -3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -21 and whose sum is -4.",
        "answer": "3 -7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 3 and whose sum is 3.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 18 and whose sum is 10.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 3 and whose sum is 1.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -6 and whose sum is 5.",
        "answer": "6 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 20 and whose sum is -9.",
        "answer": "-5 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 24 and whose sum is 10.",
        "answer": "6 4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 18 and whose sum is -9.",
        "answer": "-3 -6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 12 and whose sum is -8.",
        "answer": "-6 -2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -2 and whose sum is -1.",
        "answer": "1 -2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -15 and whose sum is -2.",
        "answer": "-5 3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 10 and whose sum is 7.",
        "answer": "5 2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -21 and whose sum is 4.",
        "answer": "-3 7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -7 and whose sum is -6.",
        "answer": "1 -7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 4 and whose sum is 1.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 4 and whose sum is -5.",
        "answer": "-4 -1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 12 and whose sum is 7.",
        "answer": "4 3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 15 and whose sum is -8.",
        "answer": "-3 -5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 21 and whose sum is -10.",
        "answer": "-3 -7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 6 and whose sum is 4.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -15 and whose sum is 8.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ],
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -14 and whose sum is -5.",
        "answer": "-7 2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -28 and whose sum is -3.",
        "answer": "4 -7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 30 and whose sum is 11.",
        "answer": "6 5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 25 and whose sum is 10.",
        "answer": "5 5",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 5 and whose sum is 6.",
        "answer": "5 1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -18 and whose sum is -3.",
        "answer": "3 -6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -30 and whose sum is 1.",
        "answer": "-5 6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 28 and whose sum is -11.",
        "answer": "-7 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 2 and whose sum is 3.",
        "answer": "2 1",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -14 and whose sum is 5.",
        "answer": "7 -2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -42 and whose sum is 1.",
        "answer": "-6 7",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -9 and whose sum is 0.",
        "answer": "-3 3",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is -20 and whose sum is 1.",
        "answer": "5 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 16 and whose sum is -8.",
        "answer": "-4 -4",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 12 and whose sum is 8.",
        "answer": "2 6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "prequad"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
  